CAPTION
<!--part-->
I congratulate you for deciding to make 2021 your best year ever. I am also humbled that you decided to spend some of your valuable time to learn online marketing from me to win over plan sponsors. You should also receive calendar invitation for 4 sessions on December 8,9, 15 & 16, all at Noon EST. Please make sure to accept them and not miss our value packed free sessions.
<!--part-->
<mjml>
    <mj-body>
        <mj-section>
        <mj-column>

            <mj-image width="100px" src="https://wellai.health/ai/img/wailogo.3f23ce58.png"></mj-image>

            <mj-divider border-color="#0059ff"></mj-divider>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial" font-size="28px">This is Daniel Satchkov from Larkspur-RiXtrema.</mj-text>
            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">I congratulate you for deciding to make 2021 your best year ever. I am also humbled that you decided to spend some of your valuable time to learn online marketing from me to win over plan sponsors. You should also receive calendar invitation for 4 sessions on December 8,9, 15 & 16, all at Noon EST. Please make sure to accept them and not miss our value packed free sessions.</mj-text>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">Why should you learn online marketing from me?</mj-text>
            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">My original area of expertise is mathematics and finance, not marketing. I founded RiXtrema as a boutique quant research firm in 2010 and we were successfully serving some of the biggest investment funds in the world. But then we lost two big clients in the space of one week and I realized that I need to learn to market our business online, so we never depend on a handful of clients again.</mj-text>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">I started reading relentlessly and by now I have taken dozens of courses and read well over 100 books on marketing. So, you will learn from my failures (and some successes, since I did sell over $11M worth of software online).</mj-text>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">Yes, 2020 was the year to forget and we cannot wait for it to be over. But what about 2021? Economic situation is harsh and old ways of winning qualified plans do not work nearly as well for advisors.</mj-text>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">That is exactly why we created FREE Win Big Plans 2021 Challenge for you with 4 in-depth training sessions on best online marketing strategies. You must win plan sponsors online in 2021 or get left behind. We will teach you how.</mj-text>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">Below is more information on the four webinars (again, you should have four invites in your inbox, one per session). Mark you calendar and I will see at the challenge!</mj-text>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">Win Big Plans 2021 Challenge consists of four live webinars:</mj-text>



            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial" font-size="18px">1. Dec. 8 at Noon/12PM EST: Learn Email Marketing Without Spending Months</mj-text>


            <mj-wrapper border="1px solid #000000" padding="5px 0px">
                <mj-section>
                    <mj-column>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">5 mistakes to avoid when writing to plan sponsors</mj-text>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">10 Types of Effective Subject Lines and more...</mj-text>
                    </mj-column>
                </mj-section>
            </mj-wrapper>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial" font-size="18px">2. Dec. 9 at Noon/12 PM EST: Discover Plan Sponsor Sales That Are Hidden in Plain Sight!</mj-text>
                

            <mj-wrapper border="1px solid #000000" padding="5px 0px">
                <mj-section>
                    <mj-column>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">A secret email that will bring you meetings immediately</mj-text>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">3 emails with highest open rates from plan sponsors</mj-text>
                    </mj-column>
                </mj-section>
            </mj-wrapper>
                

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial" font-size="18px">3. Dec. 15 at Noon/12 PM EST: A Proven Way to Set Up Your Online Presence</mj-text>
                

            <mj-wrapper border="1px solid #000000" padding="5px 0px">
                <mj-section>
                    <mj-column>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">Using surveys, assessments, marketing quizzes to drive leads</mj-text>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">5 tips to get people to leave their info on your website</mj-text>
                    </mj-column>
                </mj-section>
            </mj-wrapper>

            <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial" font-size="18px">4. Dec 16 at Noon/12 PM EST: How to Win Plans from Home on Autopilot (for tech dummies)</mj-text>

            <mj-wrapper border="1px solid #000000" padding="5px 0px">
                <mj-section>
                    <mj-column>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">How 401kFiduciaryOptimizer 3.0 wins audited plans</mj-text>
                        <mj-text font-family="Segue, Arial">How Larkspur PRO drives results on Autopilot and more</mj-text>
                    </mj-column>
                </mj-section>
            </mj-wrapper>
        
        </mj-column>
    </mj-section>
        
    </mj-body>
</mjml>